<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title/><link>https://scholz.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 20:56:13 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://scholz.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Starting Up</title><link>https://scholz.github.io/post/2020/02/starting-up/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 20:56:13 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://scholz.github.io/post/2020/02/starting-up/</guid><description>First stop: Flutter I finally managed to start working on my resolutions. The major hold back was making up my mind how to begin so that I could produce results quickly but also contribute to the complete &amp;ldquo;road map&amp;rdquo;. I actually started to read many of the different books I acquired over the last days of 2019 (all from Manning.com).
I finally settled on starting with learning Flutter.
Reasons for starting with Flutter cross platform development with the same look and feel Flutter builds for Android, iOS and web (web only recently added and still considered beta as of today) multiple projects I intend to work on would strongly benefit from cross platform learning a new modern language - Flutter is based on Dart a google developed modern language and since I haven&amp;rsquo;t learned a new language in a long time I am really looking forward to that while this may slow me down a bit I hope it compensated by the previous point due to the cross platform build I am hoping to use flutter also for the micro service development; I am really curious to see if it is only valuable for the front end or how it is advised to separate the code there; else I guess I&amp;rsquo;ll go for Python on that side Flutter hot loading seems really helpful for quick app development Looking forward to being able to develop modern web applications (I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing Javascript in the 90&amp;rsquo;s but haven&amp;rsquo;t worked in deep with any of the modern frameworks) Likely Disadvantages Learning a new language will make progress slower then expected Learning a new language and creating readable/maintainable/.</description></item><item><title>Resolutions</title><link>https://scholz.github.io/post/2020/01/resolutions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 14:18:08 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://scholz.github.io/post/2020/01/resolutions/</guid><description>Getting ahead in 2020 In the last two years I have been coordinating development efforts at a larger company. However, while I have advanced my soft skills and extended my dev ops and management knowhow, I believe there are a number of technologies which I have the strong urge to experiment with and which I have a hard time to look into at my primary job.
Therefore the major goal for this year is to enhance and deepen my knowledge in a number of exciting areas by building projects to practice and apply this know how.</description></item><item><title>Project1</title><link>https://scholz.github.io/post/2020/01/project1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 15:33:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://scholz.github.io/post/2020/01/project1/</guid><description>Describe project one</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://scholz.github.io/post/2020/01/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 14:19:43 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://scholz.github.io/post/2020/01/about/</guid><description>About Me TBD</description></item><item><title>Hello World</title><link>https://scholz.github.io/post/2020/01/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 14:06:21 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://scholz.github.io/post/2020/01/hello-world/</guid><description>Hello World! Starting this website in 2020</description></item></channel></rss>